<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="wk_learn">Learn -</string>

    <string name="wk_title_1">Personal Safety Education – SAFE UNSAFE Touch</string>
    <string name="wk_title_2">Punit Mann - De stress your mind, body &amp; soul</string>
    <string name="wk_title_3">Mind Tuning - Emotional Intelligence</string>
    <string name="wk_title_4">Bach Flower Therapy</string>
    <string name="wk_title_5">Parenting Skills</string>
    <string name="wk_title_6">Play Therapy</string>

    <string name="wk_bull_1_1">What is sexual abuse?</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_1_2">What is age appropriate sexual behavior?</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_1_3">What are the signs of a child being a victim to any kind of sexual abuse?</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_1_4">What is the right age to teach a child about good &amp; bad touch?</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_1_5">What are some do\'s &amp; don\'ts to teach good &amp; bad touch?</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_1_6">Preventive Skills to teach your child</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_1_7">How will you teach very young kids about sexuality?</string>

    <string name="wk_bull_2_1">Useful, practical stress management techniques.</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_2_2">Have a better control over your life.</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_2_3">Stress relief in the moment.</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_2_4">Reconnect with yourself.</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_2_5">How to stop worrying!</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_2_6">Prevent burnout.</string>

    <string name="wk_bull_3_1_1">Theory of Disturbance</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_3_1_2">Goal Setting</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_3_1_3">Rational v/s Irrational Beliefs</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_3_1_4">Healthy v/s Unhealthy Emotions</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_3_1_5">Scientific Approaches to deal with Disturbances</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_3_1_6">Cognitive, Emotional &amp; Behavioural Techniques to dispute Irrational Beliefs</string>

    <string name="wk_bull_3_2_1">Anger</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_3_2_2">Addiction</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_3_2_3">Self Esteem</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_3_2_4">Marital Issues</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_3_2_5">Procrastination</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_3_2_6">Problem Solving</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_3_2_7">Depressive Thinking</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_3_2_8">Performance Anxiety</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_3_2_9">Low Frustration Tolerance</string>

    <string name="wk_bull_6_1_1">
        My child is wasting most hours in the company of Idiot Boxes (computer, T.V., laptop, i-pad, cell phone, x-box)!
    </string>
    <string name="wk_bull_6_1_2">
        My child does not know how to behave well with others! S/he is very shy!
    </string>
    <string name="wk_bull_6_1_3">
        My child is very hyperactive and can\'t sit in one place!
    </string>
    <string name="wk_bull_6_1_4">My child has poor communication skills!</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_6_1_5">My child lacks focus and concentration!</string>

    <string name="wk_bull_6_2_1">Social Skills</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_6_2_2">Concentration Skills</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_6_2_3">Communication Skills</string>
    <string name="wk_bull_6_2_4">Higher Order Thinking Skills</string>

    <string name="wk_content_1_1">
        A preventive program for parents/teachers/ caretakers that will enable you to comfortably talk with your child and bring
        awareness about sexual abuse, prevent the gruesome act and stay safe.
    </string>
    <string name="wk_content_2_1">
        A Stress Management Training Program – <b>"A STRESS RELIEF GUIDE"</b> that will minimize your day to day stress
        levels – <b>STOP STRESSING, START LIVING!</b>
    </string>
    <string name="wk_content_3_1">
        Our mental health has sharply declined in the last 25 years and the chances that one will have behavioural problems such as
        lying, stealing and being disobedient, have more than doubled. The rate of emotional problems such as anxiety and depression
        has increased by 70% today. The male folk are more likely to exhibit behavioural problems and the female folk are more
        likely to suffer emotional problems. Our society breeds anxiety, depression and dysfunction. Our belief in "progress" has
        increased our expectations. The result is mass disappointment.
    </string>
    <string name="wk_content_3_2">
        It thus becomes imperative to safeguard your emotional well-being in today\'s testing and trying times. The Mind Tuning
        Training Program enables you to effectively deal with your Emotional Health. It is a 60 hour Training Program based on the
        Principles of Rational Emotive Behaviour Therapy (R.E.B.T.) by Dr. Albert Ellis and Stress Management Techniques. The
        Training Program will shed light on –
    </string>
    <string name="wk_content_3_3">
        The following issues will be dealt with during the Training -
    </string>
    <string name="wk_content_6_1">
        <b>Playstation Pluto - </b>Beneficial Fun Time, Physical Play Time, De-Tech from Gadgets
    </string>
    <string name="wk_content_6_2">
        Enroll your child for <b><i>PLAYSTATION PLUTO</i></b> if you have answered yes to any of the above and help him develop
    </string>

    <string name="sv_content_2_1_1"><b>Emotional and Behavioural Problems</b></string>
    <string name="sv_content_2_1_2">
        Symptomatic expression of emotional, interpersonal and behavioural maladjustments include nail biting, enuresis
        (bed wetting), encopresis (fecal soiling), negativism, poor social skills, emotional impairment, changing social
        scenario, depression, adjustment and/or coping difficulties, anxiety, anger issues, hyperactivity, inattention,
        lack of concentration, overtly hostile or anti-social acts, disturbed sleep patterns, addiction to electronic gadgets
        and emotional disturbances.
    </string>
    <string name="sv_content_2_1_3">
        Behavioural problems if not tackled suitably shall indeed be a great threat to the individual and his family as well as
        impacts the society at large.
    </string>
    <string name="sv_content_2_2_1"><b>Academic Problems</b></string>
    <string name="sv_content_2_2_2">
        Academic and Scholastic Backwardness may result due to either of the following –
    </string>
    <string name="sv_content_2_3"><b>Appropriate identification of the root cause followed by corresponding remedial help is a boon.</b></string>
    <string name="sv_content_2_4"><b>Book a session now to assess Emotional, Behavioural or Academic Problems and seek appropriate Guidance.</b></string>

    <string name="sv_bull_2_2_1">Learning Difficulty due to a neurological hitch or</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_2_2_2">Disturbed Family Functioning or </string>
    <string name="sv_bull_2_2_3">Emotional Dilemma or</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_2_2_4">Language Barrier.</string>

    <string name="sv_content_3_1">
        Individual Personal Counselling or Therapy is a guided process between you and a professional therapist. In these
        sessions you work towards any personal, emotional, familial, career or health related issue(s) in order to empower
        yourself.
    </string>
    <string name="sv_content_3_2">
        We at Brainwave provide a safe, caring and confidential environment to mutually work through the challenges faced by
        you. We further assist you to identify the aspects of your lives that you would like to change, set personal goals
        and understand yourself better and most importantly to cope better with your life conditions.
    </string>
    <string name="sv_content_3_3">
        You may seek therapy to cope with major life challenges and trauma, professional trials, health upheavals,
        relationship crisis or to deal with fears, phobias, anxiety, panic attacks, suicidal tendencies or depression to
        simply desiring personal growth and greater self-knowledge.
    </string>
    <string name="sv_content_3_4">
        You may work with a therapist for as many sessions as you feel the need to fortify yourself. The number of
        sessions is unique to every individuals it determined by your personal needs and goals. However, it is recommended
        to take a minimum of 5 sessions for experiencing the true quintessence of counselling.
    </string>
    <string name="sv_content_3_5"><b>Book a Counselling Session today and empower yourself…</b></string>

    <string name="sv_content_4_1">
        Need to talk to someone? Our Telephone &amp; Skype Counselling service allows you to talk to a trained therapist
        about any issue.
    </string>
    <string name="sv_content_4_2">
        Telephone &amp; Skype Counselling helps you to discuss and explore any area of your life with a therapist over
        weekly sessions of 1 hour each. The number of sessions depends on the area you wish to address and your goals.
        This is similar to Individual face – to - face Counselling, except that the sessions are on, through telephone or
        Skype.
    </string>
    <string name="sv_content_4_3"><b>Telephone &amp; Skype Counselling will benefit if:</b></string>
    <string name="sv_content_4_4"><b>When you choose telephone counselling, remember the following:</b></string>
    <string name="sv_content_4_5"><b>Book your Counselling Sessions at a time convenient to you…</b></string>

    <string name="sv_bull_4_3_1">You find it difficult to access a professional therapist in your locality.</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_4_3_2">You prefer counselling sessions over the phone.</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_4_3_3">You find it difficult to commute.</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_4_3_4">You wish to remain anonymous.</string>

    <string name="sv_bull_4_4_1">Upon making a booking, you will receive an email with the confirmation details of your
        appointment including our contact number.</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_4_4_2">As a client, you need to call the therapist at the scheduled time. Each session will be
        for one hour. If you call late, you will lose time. The therapist will end the session at the scheduled time even
        if you are late as they may have other clients scheduled next </string>
    <string name="sv_bull_4_4_3">After your first session, all subsequent session appointments will be given directly by the
        counselor.</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_4_4_4">We collect the fee in advance for your first session. To make the transaction hassle free,
        we recommend you to pay for 3 sessions after your first session. Your therapist will guide you if you have questions
        or concerns.</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_4_4_5">The payment instructions for subsequent sessions will be communicated by your therapist</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_4_4_6">Ensure you are in a noise free environment to enhance the effectiveness of the sessions</string>

    <string name="sv_content_5_1"><u>Aptitude Testing and Career Counselling</u></string>
    <string name="sv_content_5_2"><b>Career Counseling</b> is a process that will help you to know and understand yourself and
        the world of work in order to make career, educational, and life decisions. Career development is more than just
        deciding on a major and what job you want to get when you graduate.</string>
    <string name="sv_content_5_3">
        Career is encompassing an individual\'s life as it determines not only his/her job but financial as well as social
        status, lifestyle, . It is the core of human life.
    </string>
    <string name="sv_content_5_4">
        A couple of decades ago, the best career options a student had to choose were as easy as doctor, lawyer, engineer or
        a businessperson. Neither the child nor the family had to spend more time, energy or resources to worry about the
        appropriate career. It was indeed a cakewalk. However, with growing competition and with the world transforming into a
        global village, it soon became imperative to make an apt career choice. Along with the wide variety one could choose
        from, there were immense changes in the World of Work. Scores of careers became obsolete while voluminous new ones are
        available making career choice a challenging task.
    </string>
    <string name="sv_content_5_5"><u>Common Concerns to make Career Choice</u></string>
    <string name="sv_content_5_6">
        Now you are aware of the competitive, educational scenario of today\'s time. We all know that the impact of the career
        choice made today is endured lifelong. Owing to this, the youth of today experience untold confusion in order to make an
        apt career choice. At such a significant moment, it becomes imperative that one considers the following fundamental
        factors to facilitate the best career option for themselves:-
    </string>
    <string name="sv_content_5_7">
        By making a career choice based on the above, it irrefutably shall pave way for a <u>SATISFYING &amp; SUCCESSFUL FUTURE</u>.
    </string>
    <string name="sv_content_5_8">
        The <b>Aptitude Testing Program</b> will help you to take the first step in transforming your dreams into reality.
        You will be scientifically evaluated and the result will help you to become aware of your interest, skills and personal
        qualities.
    </string>

    <string name="sv_bull_5_5_1">"I have no idea what I want to do with my life."</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_5_5_2">"I don't know what to major in."</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_5_5_3">"I've narrowed it down to a couple career options, but I'm having a hard time choosing between them."</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_5_5_4">"I know what I want to major in, but I have no idea what I want to do once I graduate."</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_5_5_5">"I know what I want to do, but I'm not sure what the best major would be."</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_5_5_6">"I want to know what kinds of jobs I can get with my major."</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_5_5_7">"I don't feel like I know enough about all the different careers out there to know what I want to do."</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_5_5_8">"I like a lot of different subjects, and I keep changing my choice because I'm not sure which one is the best for me!"</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_5_5_9">"I don't like any of my classes and none of the subjects seem really appealing to me."</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_5_5_10">"I have a lot of work experience and I want to find a new career path that will build on the skills I already have."</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_5_5_11">"I was planning on going into the _______ program, but I applied and didn't get in. What do I do now?"</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_5_5_12">"My family really wants me to be a _______, but I'm not sure if that's really what I want."</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_5_5_13">"I've always planned on being a _______, but I'm wondering if it's only because that's all I know."</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_5_5_14">"I want to find a field to go into where there will always be plenty of jobs."</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_5_5_15">"I want to find a career that will allow me to provide significant financial support for my family."</string>

    <string name="sv_bull_5_6_1">Inborn skills and talents that the child possesses.</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_5_6_2">Unique behaviour and personality traits of the child.</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_5_6_3">Varied interest areas of the child.</string>

    <string name="sv_content_6_1"><b>What is Bach Flower Therapy?</b></string>
    <string name="sv_content_6_2">
        The Bach Flower Remedies is a safe and natural method of healing, discovered by Dr. Edward Bach in England. The Bach
        Flower Essences are made from flowers. They gently restore the balance between mind and body by casting out negative
        emotions such as fear, worry, hatred and indecision which interfere with the equilibrium of the being as a whole. The
        Bach Flower Remedies allow peace and happiness to return to the sufferer so that the body is free to heal itself.
    </string>
    <string name="sv_content_6_3"><b><i>Bach Flower Remedies can be used in all life situations to bring about optimism, balance, calmness and harmony.</i></b></string>
    <string name="sv_content_6_4"><b>Benefits of Bach Flower Remedies</b></string>
    <string name="sv_content_6_5">Bach Flower Remedies (BFR) aids to <b>handle any life situations</b> like – new beginnings in life, failure, how to be
        level headed in any type of situation and face any difficulty with courage and recover easily from any setback.
    </string>
    <string name="sv_content_6_6">It heals pain and suffering at <b>physical, mental, emotional, spiritual levels</b>. BFR brings about success, abundance,
        life skills to handle situations in <b>personal and professional life</b>. Flowers create harmony and help in all
        relationships, family, office, marriage, marital issues, creates abundance.
    </string>
    <string name="sv_content_6_7">Bach Flower Therapy can be used to heal the following:</string>
    <string name="sv_content_6_8"><b><u>Children</u></b></string>
    <string name="sv_content_6_9">The Bach Flowers are pure, harmonious energy frequencies that will never have negative effects; however, symptoms may be
        temporarily intensified following the initiation of Bach Flower Therapy - This means that the individual may feel worse
        for a short time as toxins are released during a clearing process often referred to as a <b><u>Healing Crisis</u></b>.
        Such a clearing process is a positive indication that equilibrium is being restored.
    </string>

    <string name="sv_bull_6_4_1"><i>Bach Flower Therapy is <u>recognized all over the world</u>.</i></string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_4_2"><i>Bach Flower Essences work as subtle, nonmaterial impulses.</i></string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_4_3"><i>It is a <u>chemical free treatment</u>.</i></string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_4_4"><i>It is useful for all kinds of <u>psycho-somatic problems, stress, strain</u> and for healing numerous diseases.</i></string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_4_5"><i>It can be used safely by <u>everyone</u> - babies, children, adults including pregnant women, animals, and plants.</i></string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_4_6"><i><u>Taking them is easy.</u> The versatility of administration ensures that the remedies may be used in all situations regardless of age or capability.</i></string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_4_7"><i>They are suitable for <u>self-healing</u>. Their harmless effects make Bach Flower Remedies a risk free system to use in self-healing.</i></string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_4_8"><i>They are <u>compatible</u> with all other forms of therapy. The Bach Flower Remedies will act harmoniously with any other form of therapy, particularly holistic therapies.</i></string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_4_9"><i>They often <u>augment other therapies</u>. In the treatment of chronic conditions, the addition of flower remedies has often brought about a crucial positive turn of events.</i></string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_4_10"><i>They help us to <u>avoid physical illness</u>.  Bach Flower Remedies do not act at the level of the physical body, but at the more subtle etheric levels that directly influence the human energy system.</i></string>

    <string name="sv_bull_6_7_1">Stress</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_7_2">Anger</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_7_3">Depression</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_7_4">Addictions</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_7_5">Sleep Disorders</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_7_6">Panic Disorders</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_7_7">Psycho-somatic Disorders</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_7_8">Self-Esteem Issues</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_7_9">Develop Soft Skills</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_7_10">Fears/Phobias/Anxiety</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_7_11">Emotional Intelligence</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_7_12">Problem Solving Skills</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_7_13">Improve Decision  Making</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_7_14">Healing Plants and pet animals.</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_7_15">During Accidents and Emergency Situations.</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_7_16">Marriage - conceiving and pregnancy issues.</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_7_17">Handling terminally ill patients including Cancer and other chronic life-threatening illnesses.</string>

    <string name="sv_bull_6_8_1">Aids infants, children and teenagers during their growing years.</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_8_2">Helps children with educational and behavioural problems such as learning difficulties – memory, inattention, hyperactive.</string>
    <string name="sv_bull_6_8_3">Help Children with Special Needs – cerebral palsy, autism, etc.</string>
</resources>