<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="bw_name"><u>BRAINWAVE PROFILE</u></string>
    <string name="bw_intro">
        Brainwave literally means rapid fluctuations of voltage between parts of the cerebral cortex that are detectable with an
        electroencephalograph. Brainwave further also refers to an idea, a notion, an inspiration, a concept, a conviction or a
        model. This means to say that a Brainwave is a clever plan or notion.
    </string>
    <string name="bw_history_title"><u>Our History</u></string>
    <string name="bw_history_info1">
        Brainwave Educational &amp; Counselling Services was started in the year 2011 to holistically cater to all those who were
        in need of resolving their emotional, behavioural and learning related concerns.
    </string>
    <string name="bw_history_info2">
        Brainwave is committed to meet the <u>personal, academic and professional needs</u> of an individual in an <u>affable</u>
        but <u>proficient</u> milieu. We take utmost care to maintain <u>confidentiality</u>. We are <u>customer centered</u>.
    </string>
    <string name="bw_history_info3">
        Brainwave offers effective counselling services to help you maintain your mental well – being.
    </string>
    <string name="bw_founder_title"><u>Founder</u></string>
    <string name="bw_founder_info1">
        Brainwave is owned and managed by Ms. Jenil Jariwala, a Counselling Psychologist, R.E.B.T. Therapist &amp; a Graphologist
        by profession. She has over 15 years of experience in the education sector.
    </string>
    <string name="bw_founder_info2">
        She has acquired her post graduate Diploma in School Counselling and a Masters in Career &amp; Developmental Counselling
        degrees from S.N.D.T. Women\'s University. She has also undertaken a foundation course on Education of Children with
        Learning Disabilities from Rehabilitation Council of India (RCI) as well as completed a basic and advanced course on
        Rational Emotive Behaviour Therapy and is now a trained R.E.B.T. Therapist for adults as well as children. She has also
        completed her basic and advanced course in Graphology.
    </string>
    <string name="bw_founder_info3">
        In the course of her career, she has coached innumerable young minds and provided them the scaffolding and buoyancy to
        accomplish their optimum abilities.
    </string>
    <string name="bw_founder_info4">
        She has been working with children, parents, teachers and adults  across all education boards; NGOs; Child Guidance Clinic;
        Remedial Centre; Guidance &amp; Counselling Department, S.N.D.T. Women\'s University, Churchgate; Distance Education
        Department, S.N.D.T. Women\'s University, Juhu. She also conducts one on one personal Counselling and Language Sessions for
        children, parents and adults to resolve academic, behavioral, emotional or career concerns.
    </string>

    <string name="bw_slogan_title"><u>Our Slogan</u></string>
    <string name="bw_slogan_info">
        "To build a healthy society" is our slogan. It appropriately reflects our attitude and approach when providing services for
        students, their parents and our education partners.
    </string>

    <string name="bw_mission_title"><u>Our Mission</u></string>
    <string name="bw_mission_info">
        We seek to develop in every individual means to lead a happy and satisfying life, to empower people to sustain well in this
        dynamic and highly competitive world using their strengths constructively. A unique plan is chalked out for every individual
        who seeks our services as we strongly believe that every individual is unique and exceptional.
    </string>
</resources>